<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Responsi 1 Mobile H1D023003</string>
    <string name="club_description">Aston Villa Football Club is a professional sports club from Birmingham, England, founded on March 14, 1874. They are one of the oldest and most successful clubs in England with a record of 7 league titles and 7 FA Cup wins. The club plays at Villa Park, a stadium with a capacity of 42,682 spectators. Aston Villa has competed at various levels of English football and won the European Cup in 1982 and 1983.</string>
    <string name="club_history_text">
        Aston Villa Football Club, founded on March 14, 1874, in Birmingham, England, stands as one of the oldest and most successful football clubs in English football history. The club\'s name derives from a villa in the Aston area of Birmingham, reflecting the region\'s rich sporting heritage.

        During the golden era of the 1890s and early 1900s, Aston Villa became a dominant force in English football. The club captured numerous league titles and FA Cups, establishing itself as a powerhouse of the era. Legendary players and managers shaped the club\'s identity during this period, with Aston Villa becoming synonymous with excellence and innovation in football tactics.

        Villa Park, the club\'s historic home stadium with a capacity of 42,682, has witnessed countless memorable moments and legendary performances. The ground\'s location in Birmingham has made it a symbol of pride for the local community for generations.

        The club\'s greatest international achievement came in 1982 when Aston Villa won the European Cup, defeating Bayern Munich 1-0 in the final. This triumph remains a pinnacle moment in English football history, showcasing Villa\'s ability to compete at the highest level of European football. The club successfully defended the trophy in 1983, cementing their place among Europe\'s elite.

        Throughout its history, Aston Villa has produced world-class talent and memorable campaigns. The club\'s traditional claret and blue colors have become instantly recognizable across football\'s global stage. With seven league titles, seven FA Cup victories, and numerous other honors, Aston Villa continues to be a respected institution in world football, attracting passionate supporters from across Birmingham and beyond.
    </string>
</resources>